ALEIX AZUELA LUENGO

-Game & Level Designer-

+34 679 591 750

aleix.azuela@gmail.com

@/in/aleixazuela/

ABOUT ME

I am a game developer currently living in Barcelona, Spain. My passions are constantly learning about game development, and creating exciting and complete experiences for others to enjoy. As of today my biggest desire is to work on an environment that will help me achieve both things.

I love making games, designing games and all the process that comes with it; the brainstorming sessions, the prototyping, talking with the team about what works and what doesn't and how to improve the game.

SKILLS

PROGRAMMING

L#

C++

SOFTWARE

Excel

Unity

Unreal

LANGUAGES

Spanish (Native)

Catalan (Native)

English (Advanced)

AWARDS

Kauil's Treasure, ENTI's Best 3rd Year Game - 2020

Kauil's Treasure, ENTI's Game of The Year - 2020

Apart, ENTI's Best Dissertation - 2021





EXPERIENCE

UNNANOUNCED TITLE

Omnidrone - Junior Game Designer

7/2021 Barcelona

Genre: RPG Responsibilities:

- · Character and Meta Design
- · Content Implementation with proprietary visual scripting tools

KAUIL'S TREASURE - PUBLISHED BY JANDUSOFT @

KT GAMES - Unity Developer, Game & Level Designer

10/2019 to 9/2020 Barcelona

Genre: 3D, Casual, Puzzle, Adventure

Responsibilities:

- One of the members defining the core game loops
- One of the members that took part in the level and puzzle design process

APART

Oblit Arts - Level & Game Designer

10/2020 to 7/2021 Barcelona

Genre: 2D, Puzzle, Platformer

Responsibilities:

- One of the main members defining the core game loops and game pillars
- ·Main responsible behind the level design process of the whole game
- ·Analyzed the user data collected after every test to improve the level's and the game's progression

EVOZOR

IMC Toys - Game Designer & Unity Developer Intern

12/2020 to 5/2021 Barcelona

Genre: MOBA
Responsibilities:

- ·Designed the moveset of the characters for the Prototype
- Designed and Balanced the Level & Battle Pass Progression for the Prototype

EDUCATION

SHORT-FILM AND DIGITAL CINEMA CREATION COURSE

BANDE A PART // 2013 Barcelona

I took on a 40-hour course where I learned the basics of Digital Cinema, and put those concepts into practice recording and editing two short-films.

BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING, NEW TECHNOLOGIES DEVELOPMENT

ENTI - UB // 2017 to 2021 Barcelona

4-year Bachelor where I learned Videogame oriented programming, design and production. During that time I was able to graduate with honors in the Level Design and Systems Design Subjects.